<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Good Vibrations Watford - Business</title>
    <link>https://gvbwatford.uk/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Good Vibrations Watford - Business</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 19:53:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://gvbwatford.uk/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Can YOU help?</title>
      <link>https://gvbwatford.uk/blog/canyouhelp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 19:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gvbwatford.uk/blog/canyouhelp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;volunteering&#34;&gt;Volunteering&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Volunteering. It feels good and you can learn lots from it. At the Croxley Studio there is so much potential for volunteers to learn some interesting new skills..&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Firstly, this is a safe, non-judgemental space to play the many instruments that are here that have been donated or restored.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We are running classes for instrument building and repair.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Everything is run on a &amp;ldquo;pay-what-you-can&amp;rdquo; donation basis.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We are in the process of building a small but usable recording setup for musicians to get creative with music creation and production software.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Do you have the interest or skills to run and maintain this &lt;em&gt;or&lt;/em&gt; do you want  to learn about it?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Most of the computers here are now running Linux which is a free, open-source operating system. Whilst this may be initially baffling for some, I&amp;rsquo;m happy to run some tutorials on this if the interest is there.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In particular, what we are finding with the Linux setups is that you can turn an otherwise older pieces of computer equipment that is destined to be e-waste into something like a file server, music jukebox or even a recording studio setup on a discarded laptop.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Linux we have also found to be very customizable for visual impairment or any other use need. It makes computers and technology to people who are otherwise excluded. we have string feels about digital exclusion. Disability happens when something like a piece of software is poorly designed.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Are you an artist or do you want to contribute to the visual identity of Good Vibrations? Do you want to learn how to build websites for FREE?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Are you a writer or do you feel YOU could write good and interesting copy for a blog?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you feel this is something you would be interesting in contributing to, please get in contact with us.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Purple Tuesday</title>
      <link>https://gvbwatford.uk/blog/purpletuesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 23:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gvbwatford.uk/blog/purpletuesday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Join us on Purple Tuesday to raise awareness of the customer experience for disabled people through music from local charity Good Vibrations 🎵 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;🗓️ Tuesday 4 November &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;🕧  12.30pm-1.30pm &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;📍 Rickmansworth High Street (Outside Iceland)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;Purple Tuesday is a special day that encourages shops, businesses, and organisations to be more welcoming and helpful to people with disabilities.&#xA;#ThreeRivers&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
